Okay, now if we can just show you a quick hands-on from the better acknowledge base service.
So I'm on the Amazon bedrock service and let me just go to the left and select for knowledge bases.
And I'm on the knowledge base service. Now what I can do is I can just click on this create
and you have the unstructured data and you have the structured data. So if I just click on this
structured data store and you just need to provide the name. So we can just leave the name as it is.
Then you have the knowledge base description. You can provide the description if you want.
Then you have the query engine. The query engine reads metadata from your structured data source
and generates the optimized SQL query. So it's going to basically read the metadata from Redshift
cluster or blue data catalog. And then next you need to provide the I am permission. So either
you can create a new service role or use an existing service role. So you're going to continue
with the new service role and then I'll just click on next. So here again you can
select the query engine connection details. So either you can use the Redshift serverless or you
can use Redshift provision. Now hopefully I'm assuming that you know Redshift is a data warehouse
solution from AWS. Now next we have to provide the authentication either I am role or you can use
the secrets manager. Now here you have to provide the storage configuration where your actual
data is stored. So either it can be Amazon Redshift database. So here you choose the database
and then provide the database. So I don't have any database. It's pretty expensive to spin up
a Redshift database. So I'm not going to do it. But the next option you have is to use the
AWS default blue catalog. So if I just click on this you can provide the blue catalog table name.
So we have the AWS blue service and under that we have this tables. So here you can see
the name data. So that's the table name you can provide. So if I just go to the blue catalog
service I don't have any tables right now but you can go to AWS blue and then here you create
a table, add table and then you just give the name of that particular table. So once you
provide the table name then you can just click on the next. So then the next step is just to review
and create. So that's how you can connect knowledge based with structured data. Now if I just go back
and if you look at the unstructured data. So here I can click on this unstructured data.
Again you just give the name. You have the IM permission. You can either create a new service
role or use an existing service role. Then if you look at some of the data source types.
Let's say for our e-learning solution all our PDFs are stored in the S3 bucket. So you can choose
that as the data source. So maybe for our e-learning solution I also want to continuously update
and see what are the new services being launched by AWS. So I can click on this web crawler and
if I just say next. So I can provide the source URLs for those AWS feeds. Then it can continuously
run at certain scheduled times and retrieve that data. Then you have other sources. Let's say
you have data in confluence. So you can connect to confluence. You can also connect to sales force,
share point and you can also have some custom connector. So let me just connect to this confluence
and show you how you can actually connect. Let me just click on next. Then I have to provide the
confluence URL which I want the knowledge base to retrieve the data from. And finally under the
unstructured data. So if you can just click on this Kendra Gen A index and then you can just give the
name here and description and then I am permission. So either use an existing Kendra Gen A
index or you can create a new Kendra Gen A index. And we're going to learn a little bit more about
Kendra in the next few lectures when we look at the vector database. But for now just remember
it was an independent NLP based enterprise search solution. But now it also has rack capabilities.
Okay, so that's pretty much it from this lecture. I'll see you in the next lecture. Thank you.